{
    "subject": "resource/Mathnet",
    "predicate": "property/director",
    "object": "James F. Golway",
    "human_readable": "James F. Golway is the director of Mathnet.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9415284395217896,
            "question": "What role does James F. Golway have at Mathnet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9106990098953247,
            "question": "Is James F. Golway involved in mathematics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8763299584388733,
            "question": "Who is the director of Mathnet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6689929366111755,
            "question": "What is the name of the institution that James F. Golway directs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.422269344329834,
            "question": "What organization does James F. Golway lead?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42190021276474,
            "question": "What is Mathnet associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3630185127258301,
            "question": "Who heads Mathnet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35919079184532166,
            "question": "What kind of work might be done at Mathnet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3409178555011749,
            "question": "Does James F. Golway have a leadership position?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2631755471229553,
            "question": "Is Mathnet a for-profit organization?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James F. Golway is the director of Mathnet.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4180_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does James F. Golway have a leadership position?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4180_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of work might be done at Mathnet?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4180_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who heads Mathnet?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4180_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4180_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4180_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4180_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4180_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4180_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4180_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4180_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4180_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4180_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4180_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that, according to the provided context information, the main characters on Mathnet are mathematicians who use mathematical skills to solve various crimes and mysteries throughout the city. However, there is no mention of a director named James F. Golway in any of the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the provided documents mention James F. Golway as the director of Mathnet. The information provided talks about the characters and background of the show \"Mathnet,\" but does not include details about its directors."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Mathnet is a fictional TV series and there were no real-life directors associated with the show in the context provided.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of James F. Golway as the director of Mathnet in any of the provided context information.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of James F. Golway being the director of Mathnet in the provided context information.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention James F. Golway as the director of Mathnet, nor does it provide any information about the directors of the show.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}